We are young!
But we have heart
Born in this world as
it all falls apart
We are strong
But we don't belong
Born in this world as
it all falls apart
I see the children in the rain
Like the parade before the pain
I see the love, I see the hate,
I see this world that we can make
I see the life, I see the sky,
Give it all to see you fly...
Yes, we wave this flag of hatred,
But you're the ones who made it
Watch the beauty of all our lies passing right before my eyes
I hear the hate in all your words,
All the wars to make us hurt
We get so sick oh so sick
We never wanted all this
Medication for the kids with no reason to live
So we march to the drums of the damned as we come
Watch it burn in the sun — we are numb
We are young!
But we have heart
Born in this world as
it all falls apart
We are strong
But we don't belong
Born in this world as
it all falls apart
And we walk among these shadows, in these streets,
This fields of battle
Take it up, we wear the medals,
Raise your hands with burning candles
Hear us whisper in the dark,
In the rain you see the spark
Feel the beating of our hearts,
Fleeting hope as we depart
All together, walk alone against all we've ever known
All we've ever really wanted
Was a place to call our home
But you take all we are; the innocence of our hearts
Made to kneel before the alter
As you tear us apart
So we march to the drums of the damned as we come
Watch it burn in the sun — we are numb
We are young, We are far
Born in this world as
it all falls apart
We are strong, We don't belong
Born in this world as
it all falls apart
We will fight or we will fall
Till the angels save us all
We are young, We are far
Born in this world as
it all falls apart
We are strong, We don't belong
Born in this world as
it all falls apart
We are young, We are far
Born in this world as
it all falls apart
We are strong, We don't belong
Born in this world as
it all falls apart